[
    {
        "type":1,
        "label":"Falso / Verdadero",
        "questions":[
            {
                "id":1, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answers":[
                    {"id":1, "label":"Verdadero"}, {"id":2, "label":"Falso"}
                ],
                "answer":1
            },
            {
                "id":2, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answers":[
                    {"id":1, "label":"Verdadero"}, {"id":2, "label":"Falso"}
                ],
                "answer":2
            },
            {
                "id":3, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answers":[
                    {"id":1, "label":"Verdadero"}, {"id":2, "label":"Falso"}
                ],
                "answer":1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "type":2,
        "label":"Opción Múltiple",
        "questions":[
            {
                "id":1, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answers":[
                    {"id":1, "label":"Opt 1"}, {"id":2, "label":"Opt 2"}, {"id":3, "label":"Opt 3"}
                ],
                "answer":1
            },
            {
                "id":2, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answers":[
                    {"id":1, "label":"Opt 1"}, {"id":2, "label":"Opt 2"}, {"id":3, "label":"Opt 3"}
                ],
                "answer":2
            },
            {
                "id":3, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answers":[
                    {"id":1, "label":"Opt 1"}, {"id":2, "label":"Opt 2"}, {"id":3, "label":"Opt 3"}
                ],
                "answer":1
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "type":3,
        "label":"Completar",
        "questions":[
            {
                "id":1, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answers":[
                    {"id":1, "label":"Opt 1"}, {"id":2, "label":"Opt 2"}, {"id":3, "label":"Opt 3"}
                ]
            },
            {
                "id":2, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answers":[
                    {"id":1, "label":"Opt 1"}, {"id":2, "label":"Opt 2"}, {"id":3, "label":"Opt 3"}
                ]
            },
            {
                "id":3, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answers":[
                    {"id":1, "label":"Opt 1"}, {"id":2, "label":"Opt 2"}, {"id":3, "label":"Opt 3"}
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "type":4,
        "label":"Abiertas",
        "questions":[
            {
                "id":1, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answer":""
            },
            {
                "id":2, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answer":""
            },
            {
                "id":3, 
                "question":"Pregunta 1", 
                "answer":""
            }
        ]
    }
]